Rin.
Hmm?
What are you going to ask Santa-san to get you?
I haven't decided yet.
If you don't make up your mind soon, it'll be too late;
he has to travel really far to get here!
Oh, really...?
C'mon now, what is it you want the most?
A lop-eared.
You already have one.
He needs friends!
Good evening!
Sorry for being late...
It's no problem!
Rin-chan!
What's that?
Hmm?
It's a Christmas tree!
Wow...
What's in here?
Ah... Something to do with work, you know?
Can I put the tree together?
Yeah.
Hurry up, Daikichi!
Okay!
This goes on top, right?
Sure does.
Ah!
What's up?
We don't have a chimney, do we?
Santa-san will be able to find his way in, so don't worry!
All right, I'll unlock the door for him!
I'm tellin' ya, it'll be fine!
Dear Santa-san,
Thank you for
the presents!
Rin
What's with the carrot?
It's for the reindeer!
I'm turning this off, all right?
Just a little longer...
Santa-san only comes to the houses of sleeping children!
Huh?! Turn the light off, quick!
Yeah, yeah.
Dear Santa-san,
Thank you for
the presents!
Rin
I really wanted to meet Santa too.
Rin, let's eat!
Okay!
Thank you too, Mr. Reindeer!
「Dear Santa-san」